TAYLOUR KROEKER

J 604-700-6116 | ★ taylour.em@gmail.com | ↑ tailorem | ♦ Vancouver, BC

SUMMARY

A junior full-stack web developer with a great appreciation for collaborative problem solving. Excited by beautiful & functional interfaces, efficient & sustainable systems and forever seeking to expand my horizons. My 5 year history in the retail industry encouraged me to develop my sense of dedication, persistence and enthusiasm, as well as strong interpersonal and organizational skills.

PROJECTS

Bendito - A responsive, team-built food-ordering and order management application that communicates with clients via SMS. Built with JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Express, Twilio API, Ajax, jQuery and HTML/CSS/SASS with Bootstrap.

Relephant - A single-page Twitter-clone application allowing users to anonymously create posts. Created using JavaScript, Express, Node.js, MongoDB, jQuery, Ajax and HTML/CSS and hosted on Heroku.

TinyApp - A multi-page app allowing users to create and share shortened URLs. Coded following RESTful practices, using Node.js and Express for server-side implementation and HTML, EJS templating and custom CSS for front-end views.

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs, Vancouver — Web Development Bootcamp

JULY 2018-SEPTEMBER 2018

- Intensive full-stack web development bootcamp
- 500+ hours of mentor-assisted project-based programming
- Building apps using HTML/CSS, JavaScript, SQL, React and more

EXPERIENCE

Omer DeSerres, Vancouver — Assistant Manager

APRIL-AUGUST 2016 & MARCH 2017-JULY 2018

- Managed daily store operations and staff scheduling
- Supported, trained and worked alongside staff in all departments
- Communicated daily with head office, suppliers and other locations

Omer DeSerres. Vancouver — Merchandiser

JULY 2014-MARCH 2017

- Designed effective product layouts based on customer behavior
- Created compelling displays through analysis of inventory and sales data
- Led restructure of store layout and assisted setup of new location

Omer DeSerres, Vancouver — Sales Associate

OCTOBER 2012-JULY 2014

- Encouraged customers to return by creating a welcoming atmosphere
- Utilized arts knowledge to assist customers in making informed decisions
- Operated POS system, maintained store stock and cleanliness

Environmental Youth Alliance, Vancouver — Youth Mentor

JULY 2012-JULY 2013

- Guided youth at community-oriented events such as market plant giveaways
- Prepared weekly informational materials and led activities to teach gardening skills
- Aided in maintenance of community garden space

SKILLS

JavaScript HTML5 CSS

Git VCS Node.js Knex.is Express JSON i0ueru Ajax React SASS MongoDB PostgreSQL Mocha/Chai unit testing REST Responsive design 00P

Photoshop Lightroom